<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Books>
  <Book Code="101">
    <Title>How To Be A Man</Title>
    <Author>Jim Nilson</Author>
    <Description>It is a physological book.</Description>
    <Price>260</Price>
    <Discount>15</Discount>
    <InStock>10</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="102">
    <Title>Tarzan</Title>
    <Author>Michael Sanford</Author>
    <Description>It is an interesting legend.</Description>
    <Price>190</Price>
    <InStock>0</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="103">
    <Title>The Migrant</Title>
    <Author>Richard Bridges</Author>
    <Description>It is a book about the problems of migrants.</Description>
    <Price>350</Price>
    <Discount>15</Discount>
    <InStock>5</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="110">
    <Title>Diapers</Title>
    <Author>Michael Sanford</Author>
    <Description>Are you a busy parent who needs help trying to manage it all? Let busy mom of two, Jan Cornell teach you how to live your life in a more simple and meaningful way with her fun, practical, quick and easy hacks. There are better and more efficient ways to manage both your life as a busy parent and your household! If you are a busy parent in the midst of chaos, this book was written for you!</Description>
    <Price>145</Price>
    <InStock>8</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="120">
    <Title>Subtitle</Title>
    <Author>Marie Kelly</Author>
    <Description>When Tara James finds out her soon-to-be-famous movie star sister needs her, she drops everything to rush to her aid.  While the twins might have very different lives, it is the fact they are identical which allows her to stand in for Susan Sunny. </Description>
    <Price>115</Price>
    <InStock>25</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="119">
    <Title>The Perfectionist</Title>
    <Author>Rafe Oropella</Author>
    <Description>The Perfectionist is an ex-CIA operative who isn’t ready for retirement yet. His lifelong dream is to seek out and find the lost Nazi gold, smuggled during World War II. To do so, he needs a large amount of capital. </Description>
    <Price>95</Price>
    <InStock>25</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="114">
    <Title>Joy of Life Paperback</Title>
    <Author>Rafe Oropella</Author>
    <Description>
    </Description>
    <Price>100</Price>
    <InStock>30</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="118">
    <Title>They Were Shining</Title>
    <Author>Marie Kelly</Author>
    <Description>Students went into the community and interviewed the street vendors themselves, getting a first-hand account of their stories. Students then wrote these stories, either assuming the first person, or telling a third person narrative.</Description>
    <Price>190</Price>
    <InStock>27</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="113">
    <Title>After June</Title>
    <Author>Thomasin Heyworth</Author>
    <Description>Sixty-seven-year-old Ben Willows prefers the company of a dog to that of most people. So, now that his wife June, an exception in the people category with whom hes shared most of his life, has died, he assumes hell live out his days keeping to himself and making the best of what a solitary life has to offer.</Description>
    <Price>270</Price>
    <Discount>25</Discount>
    <InStock>29</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="112">
    <Title>To Free the Fox</Title>
    <Author>Marquel Sherry</Author>
    <Description>Alitha Helgren a college student, whose life so far has been rocky, but ordinary, goes to spend the summer at her deceased grandmothers cottage. While there she begins to experience some unusual things.</Description>
    <Price>250</Price>
    <Discount>15</Discount>
    <InStock>27</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="111">
    <Title>The Imposter</Title>
    <Author>Sarah Pratt</Author>
    <Description>Amidst the chaos left in back alleyways and side streets, the Marker wages war against corruption in the crime-ridden metropolitan city of Ashden.</Description>
    <Price>420</Price>
    <InStock>0</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="109">
    <Title>Ten Minute Tales</Title>
    <Author>Mavis Brown</Author>
    <Description>Ten Minute Tales will be invaluable to anyone with children aged 3 to 8 years old. </Description>
    <Price>400</Price>
    <Discount>15</Discount>
    <InStock>8</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="108">
    <Title>The White Tree</Title>
    <Author>Mark C. Brown</Author>
    <Description>It is beautiful story for all people.</Description>
    <Price>310</Price>
    <Discount>30</Discount>
    <InStock>2</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="107">
    <Title>Favourite Carols</Title>
    <Author>Ruth Finnegan</Author>
    <Description>The first collection specifically of the WORDS of well-known carols since John Stainers shorter  volume a century ago: as good for  street singers  we know the tunes already but need the words -</Description>
    <Price>230</Price>
    <Discount>10</Discount>
    <InStock>2</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="106">
    <Title>The Snarky Puppy</Title>
    <Author>Snarky Puppy</Author>
    <Description>The tiers are shifting.  The omniverses are under attack.  And only one man has the chromosomes to make things right.  Or does he?</Description>
    <Price>400</Price>
    <InStock>1</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="105">
    <Title>Fatherhood</Title>
    <Author>Omar Epps</Author>
    <Description>Author and world renowned actor Omar Epps chronicles his journey from humble beginnings in Brooklyn, New York, to the bright lights of Hollywood. </Description>
    <Price>180</Price>
    <InStock>5</InStock>
  </Book>
  <Book Code="104">
    <Title>Red Tide</Title>
    <Author>John Alexander</Author>
    <Description>pace Navy Lieutenant Sally Fenway survives a terrorist attack on Times Square in New York City.</Description>
    <Price>150</Price>
    <InStock>2</InStock>
  </Book>
</Books>